<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfArticle xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Article>
    <ID>101</ID>
    <Title>May Pendant Shade, Neon Blue</Title>
    <Price>45</Price>
    <Picture>may_pendant_light_blue_pl.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>Inspired by fashion runways, these shades are designed to stand out. The neon accents lets you show off your style, just turn them on and strike a pose.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>102</ID>
    <Title>May Pendant Shade, Neon Orange</Title>
    <Price>19</Price>
    <Picture>may_pendant_light_orange_pl.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>If you already have pendant lighting set up in your home then you’re good to go. There’s no need to call an electrician, these shades can be fitted quickly and easily.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>103</ID>
    <Title>May Pendant Shade, Neon Pink</Title>
    <Price>29</Price>
    <Picture>may_pendant_light_pink_pl.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>Looking to brighten up a room? Try hanging a series above your dining table, give your living space an arty appeal or add a touch of fun in a classic white bedroom.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>104</ID>
    <Title>Hue Pendant Shade, Grey &amp; Copper</Title>
    <Price>29</Price>
    <Picture>hue_pendant_light_grey_pl_1.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>It’s doesn’t matter if it’s day or night, Hue looks super sleek on or off. The shade is made with cotton in a soft grey or deep navy. The reflective copper liner throws the light further and gives any room or hallway a warm glow.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>105</ID>
    <Title>Broadway Star Table Lamp, Black</Title>
    <Price>99</Price>
    <Picture>broardway_small_star_pl_3.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>Get some classic New York glamour with the Broadway. We dare you to try and find lighting with more statement.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>106</ID>
    <Title>Broadway Arrow Table Lamp, Black</Title>
    <Price>89</Price>
    <Picture>broardway_arrow_pl_5.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>Table or wall? It's your choice - with handy wall fittings and a cable mounted switch, you can set it up exactly as you like.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>107</ID>
    <Title>Broadway Arrow Table Lamp, Black</Title>
    <Price>169</Price>
    <Picture>chicago_lamp_blacksilver_pl_2_2.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>Bring some vintage Hollywood glamour into your home with this tripod floor lamp. Inspired by film sets from days gone by.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>108</ID>
    <Title>Navy Tripod Floor Lamp, Black</Title>
    <Price>99</Price>
    <Picture>3_navy_black__1.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>This lamp adds a contemporary, nautical edge to your look. Made with a seafaring tripod structure and chrome metal detailing.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>109</ID>
    <Title>Alfred Tripod Floor Lamp, White</Title>
    <Price>149</Price>
    <Picture>alfred_tripod_floor_lamp_white.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>A statement piece with an iconic tripod shape and sleek, shuttered shade. Inspired by studio lights from Hollywood's golden era</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>110</ID>
    <Title>Cohen Double Floor Lamp, White and Natural Oak</Title>
    <Price>119</Price>
    <Picture>cohen_double_light_white_pl_2.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>A true statement piece, the doubled headed industrial design is softened by the offset of natural wood and bold single colours.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>111</ID>
    <Title>Cohen Table Lamp, Memphis Blue and Natural Oak</Title>
    <Price>55</Price>
    <Picture>cohen_table_lamp_blue_pl.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>This table lamp is all about the smart detailing, the shade top and handle are both finished in American Oak. It's fun and modern and would be an ideal addition to a loft apartment or city pad.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>112</ID>
    <Title>Lab Table Lamp, Teal, Deep Grey and Mustard</Title>
    <Price>129</Price>
    <Picture>lab_table_lamp_mustard_grey_blue_pl.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>Designed to steal the show and be the focal point of the room. Each piece of glass is mouth blown and hand moulded. Every curve and air bubble seen through the glass are marks of a handmade piece.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>113</ID>
    <Title>Austin Cluster Pendant, Copper</Title>
    <Price>79</Price>
    <Picture>austin_cluster_light_pl.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>The shape of the shades is inspired by space-age interiors of the 60s. The spiral of globe shades creates concentrated pools of light while the decorative air vents at the top of the piece diffuse the glow for an ambient uplight.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>114</ID>
    <Title>Austin Spot Wall Light, Copper</Title>
    <Price>69</Price>
    <Picture>austin_spot_wall_light_copper_pl.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>Classic, chic, modern, industrial. The copper trend is one of the most versatile and fun to play around with. These wall lights are the ideal addition to any stylish home.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>115</ID>
    <Title>Cage Pendant, Black</Title>
    <Price>99</Price>
    <Picture>cage_pedant_light_black_1.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>Add a unique and stylish touch to your home with this lantern-shaped pendant light - a modern addition to any living space.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>116</ID>
    <Title>Hive Pendant Light, Soft Green</Title>
    <Price>59</Price>
    <Picture>hive-pedant-light-soft-green.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>This geometric pendant light will bring a modern edge to any living space.</Description>
  </Article>
  <Article>
    <ID>117</ID>
    <Title>Freddie Pendant Shade, Black</Title>
    <Price>45</Price>
    <Picture>freddie_hanging_lights_black.jpg</Picture>
    <Category>Lamps</Category>
    <Description>Like its namesake, the Freddie shade commands attention. Designed with bold, geometric patterns, it softly illuminates bedrooms and living spaces.</Description>
  </Article>
</ArrayOfArticle>